ED]
[ED]
I'm about to start shooting a commercial for Workstaff.
It's our first time, and the first time for BTG, so I'm really nervous and excited, but we're all going to do our best.
It looks like they are going to make a composite of us dancing on this miniature.
The pastel colors are so cute.
I don't know how it will turn out, but I'm really looking forward to it.
Hey, can I ask each of you to speak one at a time during the practice?
Yes.
If you want to work like me, you should be a work stuffer!
Yes, sir. And I mean it, with a real sense of humor. That's good.
Let's go one more time. Yes, cheer up.
Good, yes.
If you want to work the way I do, Work Stuff!
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
Okay, let's do it again. Let's go one more time.
One more practice.
Okay, yes.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
If you want to work actively, Work Stuff!
That's what I'm talking about.
What?
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
I like making things, so I'm going to do something like "I like making things, so I'm going to do Work Stuff!
So, please practice it in your mind while looking at the contest.
Please practice it in your mind while looking at the contest.
Please do that.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to look at it as if Yuriyan is going to make adjustments.
I was practicing my dance.
This waku waku waku, the staff's dance was very difficult.
I still don't know whether to turn my neck vertically like this or horizontally like this.I don't know yet whether I'm going to turn my head this way vertically or that way horizontally.
I have to keep both in mind until the show.
So I will practice.
It's more the fault of the 7 month tumor than my oral technique that makes me do the strip where the river floats.
I don't even have the words, the lyrics are more all over the place than the name, and even more people sing it together with the B title.
I am from the earth now keep going
I'm new.
Yellow, yellow people.
Doesn't it look good?
What do you mean?
Does it look good?
Lemon-y.
I see.
What do you do for a living?
What job? What job?
Efmarie, you know.
That's the moving company.
That's right.
I see.
I'll leave this to you.
I'm dry.
Oh, I see.
Let's go to work.
Let's go get a box of potatoes.
Okay, you want to start shaking the sweet potatoes?
No, I don't want to start with the swing.
You mean the boxes?
That's right.
I can't handle bugs.
I can't stop. I can't stop that much.
It's kind of half-baked.
Your mouth is smiling.
It suits you.
He's cute.
I got it.Yay!
I feel like a chick.
That's a compliment.
No, no, no. In a manner of speaking.
It looks good.
Yay, you're a chick.
Chickens and mallow?
Carrots.
I'll have a carrot.
Oh, no.
Predator.
Carrots.
Who are you?
Miss Pienaar.
Pienaar?
Please, please, please.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fold.
Check, come in.
Clear. I'm ok. We have a new unit.
I'll get it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
i'm in, i'm in, i'm in, i'm in, i'm in, i'm in, thank you, please.
Thank you!
ok, ok, ok, ok, ok...
All dysfunction
None Fyont
Subtitle Editor's Report
Someday people will come.
Yes, check.
Laughter
LaughterLaughter.
The look on his face the moment there was a cut.
laughter
I thought I was going to die.
It was fun to watch.
It was cute.
♪ The air is strange ♪
♪ I am now ♪
Sorry!
I danced without fail.
I'm so excited to see Aoi's back.
I see.
He has the most excited expression.
Oh, I don't like it.
You don't like it?
Strong. Strong.
Strong?
Strong.
Strong-willed.
He's the oldest.
Okay, let's try the bird.
Oh, you're giving it to me.
Well, thank you... for the loan.
Okay, bye.
I'm thrilled.
Oh, cute.
Worked.
Movement strong.
Worked it.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Heart.
Exciting.I'm excited.
I see.
Okay, last leader.
Last leader.
Oh!
Se-no.
I did the work.
It was a dud.
Mostly
Come on.
I said big trey, so liven it up.
Get it right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're the leader.
I knew you could do it.
Scary face.
Look at this face.
The winner is...
Himari!
Pappa-pappa!
You, you, you!
How do you feel?
Oh, I'm scared.
I'm afraid of violence.
No, I didn't.
It was really nice to meet you.
I'm sorry.
How are you doing?
I made you a cup.
He's not coming.
Nyatz!
My elbow's stuck, too.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Can I do it once for Nyatz Nyatz?
Why?Why?
It doesn't taste so good.
I'm excited.
What? Are you excited?
I'm scared.
The next day, I go to the studio.
Yellow gloves.
Everyone tries to take off their gloves at every turn.
I understand.
I'm scared.
Really scary.
All right, let's begin.
Thank you for watching!
I'm done!
Now I'm going to do a solo shoot.
I'm a little nervous, but I have some lines to say, so I'll do my best.
I'm going to try to get it just in time, and I'm going to do my best with my facial expressions.
How many seconds?
2.5 seconds, and I'm aiming for exactly 2.5 seconds.
I like to make axes, and I'm a work stuffer!
Now that's a little spill, isn't it?
That was a little bit of a spill.
I like making axes, I'm a work stuffer!
Maybe that's natural.
I like making axes, I'm Work Stuff!
Mom!
Can we go faster?
Now that's a little bit of movement, but I'm keeping one.
Anything else?
All right, start!
Start!
I like to make axes. I'm a work stuffer!
Yes, cut!
Yes, okay.
I'm scared of stories.
I'm scared without you guys.I'm scared without you guys.
Yo, start!
If you want to be active, Markstaff is the place to be!
Yes, cut!
Cut.
The last one was a bit early.
Yes, yes, start!
If you work actively, Work Stuff!
Cut!
We'll continue after this.
Please look like you're having a lot of fun.
Yes, start!
Here comes the cut.
Cut!
Let's see the teeth first.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, let's start!
Cut!
It looks good.
Yes, it's good.
Now that's good.
Okay, here's one for you.
Well, he said he could do it.
Can I change it to a title?
May I? Yes!
Cut!
A little more intense.
Oh, it won't fall off.
Get ready!
Here we go!
Here we are.
The two of us weren't at the same height.
Please give me a little bit of height.
Yes, there.
All right,Yo,
Here you go.
Yes, check.
Yes, OK.
Thank you very much.
Let's start the next changeover like this.
Now, I would like to eat my lunch.
Partner, take two.
Okay, partner, yo, start!
Aah!
I'm tired.
I'm stuck.
Start!
Ah!
I dropped it.
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
High cut!
Staff.
After this, a little high, spill.
A little long.
Start.
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
Start.
Yes, cut!
Yes, check.
Yes, OK.
If you want to improve your skills, Work Stuff!
Okay, so now the cut is OK, and that's all for Break Time Girl, Backup Dancer, and Thank You for the Club Cup.
All shooting is finished!All the shooting is finished!
Thank you very much!
It all happened so fast.
It was really fun.
We all did our own cuts and selfies,
It was an experience that made me feel like a major artist.
Also, it was great to see ourselves in a TV commercial.
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's true.
If you think about it calmly, it would be dangerous.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
It's bad, isn't it?
But what if it's too little?
What should we do?
Enjoy the commercial!
Enjoy!
Enjoy yourselves!